Youth is innocent until proven guilty.
Wasted on the Young is a drama, thriller, romance film directed by Ben C. Lucas.
When a high school party goes dangerously off the rails, one
teenager finds that revenge is just a computer click away.
Xandrie, played by Adelaide Clemens.
Zack, played by Alex Russell.
Ella, played by Geraldine Hakewill.
Simone, played by Georgina Haig.
Cyber Bully, played by Lisa Bennett.
Darren, played by Oliver Ackland.
Wasted on the Young is a 2011 Australian thriller film directed by Ben C.
Lucas and starring Oliver Ackland, Adelaide Clemens, and Alex Russell.
Shot by cinematographer Dan Freene, it tells the story of a traumatic high school
incident that sets off a fatal chain of events for two brothers.
The film was shot in 2009 at an ultra modern mansion in City Beach and at
Edith Cowan University's Mount Lawley and Joondalup campuses.
The film received $750,000 in ScreenWest funding through its West Coast
Visions initiative, as well as funding from Screen Australia.
The tone is emotional and intense.